



kuanyshboranbayev.herokuapp.com github.com/kboranbayev

linkedin.com/in/kuanyshboranbayev

Full Stack Developer Network Analyst DevOps

## WHO AM I?

Dedicated and self-motivated Full Stack Developer with 4 years experience and proficiency in the following: Nodejs, Reactjs, C, HTML and CSS, and AWS serverless architecture arsenal. Very familiar and experienced in modern MVC frameworks and SDLC. An excellent team worker.



# **EXPERIENCE**

2017 - 4/2017 **Back-End Developer** part time

**Denis Boyd & Associates** Designed and developed web application run by a group of psychologists. The web application

offers end users 25-day boot camp for strengthening mental health.

node.js / expressjs / mongodb / AWS EC2

2018 - 2019 Full Stack Developer Solo Project

Front-end developed using ReactJS and back-end is running using ExpressJS, and hosted on Heroku applications. Back-end is connected to Mongo DB which hosted on remote mLab server.

reactjs / semantic-ui / nodejs / mongodb / heroku / api

10/2019 - 2020 Full Stack Developer TheSheph.com Project

Designed back-end of the web application and implemented DB server on remote proxy server.

Implemented easily understandable REST API calls for front-end access.

reactjs / bootstrap / nodejs / AWS EC2 / heroku / mongodb / api

# **EDUCATION**

9/2019 - 4/2021 **Bachelor of Technology**  British Columbia Institute of Technology

Network Security Applications Development

1/2016 - 12/2017 **Diploma** 

British Columbia Institute of Technology

Computer Systems Technology with Cloud Computing Option

2013 - 2015 **Applied Science Certificate** Columbia College

### **LANGUAGES**

#### **HOBBIES**

### **NON PROFIT**

English - proficient Russian - proficient Kazakh - native

- creating web applications for a variety of purposes

- cloud computing development

- watching tv shows and movies

I help people to create a static portfolio websites.